drivingsales.com 2019-04-22

# DrivingSales

Welcome to DrivingSales.com (“DrivingSales”) and DrivingSalesData.com (“DrivingSales Data”), the online services of DrivingSales, Inc. (“DrivingSales, Inc.” “we,” or “us”). Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect information that applies to our Services, and your choices about the collection and use of your information.

Click on the links below to jump to each section:

  1. How We Collect and Use Information
  2. Sharing of Your Information
  3. How We Store and Protect Your Information
  4. Your Choices about Your Information
  5. Children's Privacy
  6. Links to Other Websites and Services
  7. How to Contact Us
  8. Changes to Our Privacy Policy

### 1\. HOW WE COLLECT AND USE INFORMATION

Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in the [DrivingSales Terms of Use](http://www.drivingsales.com/tos) or the [DrivingSales Data Terms of Use](http://drivingsalesdata.com/site/tos?__hstc=230076931.057e86b1d1e7c8a68749e187a19a5a31.1455211588565.1456349257173.1456512567736.9&__hssc=230076931.3.1456512567736&__hsfp=1117272239), as applicable.

We collect the following types of information about you:

**Information you provide us directly:**  We ask for certain information such as your username, first and last name, birth date, phone number and e-mail address when you register for a DrivingSales or DrivingSales Data account, or if you correspond with us. We may also retain any messages you send through the Services, and may collect information you provide in User Content you post to the Services. We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Services.

**Analytics information.**  We may directly collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Services. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit and other information that assists us in improving the Services. We collect and use this analytics information in aggregate form such that it cannot reasonably be manipulated to identify any particular individual user.

**Cookies information:**  When you visit the Services, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets DrivingSales and DrivingSales Data help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Services (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on the Services), and allow us or our business partners to track your usage of the Services over time. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Services may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

**Log file information:**  Log file information is automatically reported by your browser or mobile device each time you access the Services. When you use our Services, our servers automatically record certain log file information. These server logs may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Services, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

**Clear gifs/web beacons information:**  When you use the Services, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to anonymously track the online usage patterns of our Users. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information is allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Services.

**Commercial and marketing communications:**  We use the information we collect or receive to communicate directly with you. We may send you emails containing newsletters, promotions and special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you will be given the option to opt out or change your preferences. We also use your information to send you Services-related emails (e.g., account verification, purchase and billing confirmations and reminders, changes/updates to features of the Services, technical and security notices). You may not opt out of Services-related e-mails.

**Use of certain service type information we collect about you:**  We use or may use cookies, log file, and clear gifs information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) to provide and monitor the effectiveness of our Services; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems; (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in; and (g) to provide advertising to your browser or device.

### 2\. SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATION

We will not rent or sell your information into third parties outside DrivingSales, Inc. and its group companies (including any parent, subsidiaries and affiliates) without your consent, except as noted below:

**Who we may share your information with:**  We may share your information with third-party business partners for the purpose of providing the Services to you. Those business partners will be given limited access to your information as is reasonably necessary to deliver the Services, and we will require that such third parties comply with this Privacy Policy.

**Who you may chose to share your User Content with:**  Any information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Services, such as User Content, becomes available to the public, as controlled by any applicable privacy settings. Subject to your profile and privacy settings as applicable, any User Content that you make public is searchable by other Users. If you remove information that you posted to the Services, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Services, or if other Users have copied or saved that information.

**What happens in the event of a change of control:**  We may buy or sell/divest/transfer the DrivingSales, Inc. (including any shares in the DrivingSales, Inc.), or any combination of its products, services, assets and/or businesses. Your information such as customer names and email addresses, User Content and other user information related to the Services may be among the items sold or otherwise transferred in these types of transactions. We may also sell, assign or otherwise transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, acquisitions, bankruptcies, dissolutions, reorganizations, liquidations, similar transactions or proceedings involving all or a portion of the DrivingSales, Inc.

**Instances where we are required to share your information:**  DrivingSales, Inc. will disclose your information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (b) to enforce the DrivingSales Terms of Use [link]or the DrivingSales Data Terms of Use [link], or to protect the security or integrity of our Services; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of DrivingSales, Inc., our Users or others.

**Sharing certain service type information we collect about you:**  We may share certain service type information, including information obtained through tools such as cookies, log files and clear gifs (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.): (i) with our third-party business partners for the purposes described in the section above on  **“How We Collect and Use Information.”**  We may also aggregate or otherwise strip data of all personally identifying characteristics and may share that aggregated, anonymized data with third parties.

**Ads on DrivingSales and DrivingSales Data:**  We may also share certain information such as your browser and cookie data and other data relating to your use of our Services with our business partners to deliver advertisements (“ads”) that may be of interest to you. DrivingSales, Inc. may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the Services. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser the ads and ad links that appear on the Services, and will automatically receive your IP address when they do so. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript and clear gifs, see above) to compile information about your browser’s visits and usage patterns on the Services, and to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize the advertising content. DrivingSales. Inc. does not sell, rent, or share the information we collect directly from you or about you from third parties with these third-party ad servers or ad networks for such parties’ own marketing purposes.

Please note that an advertiser may ask DrivingSales or DrivingSales Data to show an ad to a certain audience of Users (e.g., based on demographics or other interests). In that situation, DrivingSales and Driving Sales Data determine the target audience and serve the advertising to that audience and only provide anonymous aggregated data to the advertiser. If you respond to such an ad, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach.

The DrivingSales, Inc. Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers or contact such advertisers for more information.

### 3\. HOW WE STORE AND PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

**Storage and Processing:**  Your information collected through the Services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which DrivingSales, Inc. or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. DrivingSales, Inc. may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which DrivingSales, Inc. or its parent, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Keeping your information safe:**  DrivingSales, Inc. cares about the security of your information, and uses commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected through the Services. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from DrivingSales, Inc., at all times. However, DrivingSales, Inc. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to DrivingSales, Inc. or guarantee that information on the Services may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of third party sites and services that you add to the DrivingSales, Inc. Services, such as social networks. DrivingSales, Inc. is not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

**Compromise of information:**  In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, DrivingSales, Inc. will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

### 4\. Your Choices About Your Information

**You control your account information and settings:**  You may update your account information and email-communication preferences at any time by logging into your account and changing your profile settings. You can also stop receiving promotional email communications from us by clicking on the “unsubscribe link” provided in such communications. We make every effort to promptly process all unsubscribe requests. As noted above, you may not opt out of Services-related communications (e.g., account verification, purchase and billing confirmations and reminders, changes/updates to features of the Services, technical and security notices). If you have any questions about reviewing or modifying your account information, you can contact us directly at[support@DrivingSales.com](mailto:support@drivingsales.com) or [support@DrivingSalesData.com](mailto:support@drivingsalesdata.com), as applicable.

**Opting out of collection of your information for Tracking / Advertising:**  Please refer to your mobile device or browser’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. Depending on your type of device, it may not be possible to delete or disable tracking mechanisms on your mobile device. Note that disabling cookies and/or other tracking tools prevents DrivingSales, Inc. or its business partners from tracking your browser’s activities in relation to the Services, and for use in targeted advertising activities by third parties. However, doing so may disable many of the features available through the Services. If you have any questions about opting out of the collection of cookies and other tracking/recording tools, you can contact us directly at [support@DrivingSales.com](mailto:support@drivingsales.com) or [support@DrivingSalesData.com](mailto:support@drivingsalesdata.com), as applicable.

**How long we keep your User Content:**  Following termination or deactivation of your User account, as applicable, DrivingSales, Inc. may retain your profile information and User Content for a commercially reasonable time for backup, archival, or audit purposes.

### 5\. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

DrivingSales and DrivingSales Data do not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Users. The Services and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [support@DrivingSales.com](mailto:support@drivingsales.com) or [support@DrivingSalesData.com](mailto:support@drivingsalesdata.com), as applicable.

### 6\. LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES AND SERVICES

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Services, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Services to another website, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link or advertisement on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible and we do not control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party website or service and you allow such a third-party access to you User Content you do so at your own risk. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources other than through the Services.

### 7\. HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Services, please contact us at [support@DrivingSales.com](mailto:support@drivingsales.com) or [support@DrivingSalesData.com](mailto:support@drivingsalesdata.com), as applicable.

### 8\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

DrivingSales, Inc. may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect the changes in our business and practices, and so you should review this page periodically. When we change the policy in a material manner we will let you know and update the ‘last modified’ date at the bottom of this page.

This privacy policy was last modified on January 4, 2013.
